<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>BSides Wellington</title>
    <link>https://www.bsides.nz/</link>
    <description>Recent content on BSides Wellington</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.bsides.nz/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About BSides Wellington</title>
      <link>https://www.bsides.nz/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.bsides.nz/about/</guid>
      <description>What is Security BSides? BSides is a community-driven framework for building events for and by information security community members. The goal is to expand the spectrum of knowledge and understanding through conversation by creating opportunities for individuals to both present and participate in an intimate atmosphere that encourages discussion and collaboration. It is an intense event with discussions, demos, and interaction from participants. It is where conversations on the next big thing are happening.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Call for Papers</title>
      <link>https://www.bsides.nz/cfp/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.bsides.nz/cfp/</guid>
      <description>Call For Papers (CFP) is now closed
In true Security B-Sides (BSides) form, BSides Wellington is a community security conference. What better way to pay tribute to that community than inviting consultants, hackers, hobbyists, academics, students, and public-sector type folks to a conference hall to share their ideas, experiences and knowledge?
All submissions will be reviewed by our CFP review board. We will be accepting talks in 2 rounds. So, if you have something to say, submit your talk now because the second round will be a little less flexible in terms of time/format/topics.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Code of Conduct</title>
      <link>https://www.bsides.nz/coc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.bsides.nz/coc/</guid>
      <description>The short version TL;DR BSides Wellington is dedicated to providing a harassment-free conference experience for everyone. We encourage all participants to make each other feel welcome and included in activities throughout the conference. We do not tolerate harassment of conference participants in any form. Conference participants violating these rules may be sanctioned or expelled from the conference without a refund at the discretion of the conference organisers.
The long version Code of Conduct</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Event</title>
      <link>https://www.bsides.nz/event/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.bsides.nz/event/</guid>
      <description>Venue &amp;amp; Logistics Shed 6, 4 Queens Wharf, Te Aro, Wellington 6140
23 &amp;amp; 24th of November 2017
Shed 6 is in the middle of town, near the train station, and close to many cafes, pubs, and hotels. It will be broken into multiple talk/workshop areas, consisting of a large talk track, a smaller talk/workshop track, and a third room for other events.
Schedule of Events BSides Wellington will take place with two tracks, one in each room, and a breakout room for people to chill in.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Financial Aid</title>
      <link>https://www.bsides.nz/financialaid/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.bsides.nz/financialaid/</guid>
      <description>The Diversity and Financial Aid fund is open until the 21st of November. Apply here!
The BSidesWLG organisers care about making a diverse and inclusive security conference. This means extending a helping hand to those who need it, whether due to financial need or as members of traditionally underrepresented groups at such events.
Diversity and inclusion are personal to us as, between the four organisers, we represent four different decades, women, LGBTQ, and immigrants.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Schedule</title>
      <link>https://www.bsides.nz/schedule/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.bsides.nz/schedule/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sponsorship</title>
      <link>https://www.bsides.nz/sponsor/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.bsides.nz/sponsor/</guid>
      <description>Interested in Sponsoring? Click here to download our sponsorship information kit
BSidesWLG 2017 is not possible without sponsors! Just as BSidesWLG will provide a forum for participants to engage with others in the Wellington and wider New Zealand information security community, it will also facilitate a way for sponsors to engage our community of participants. The nature of our smaller, community-focused event provides our sponsors with the opportunity to be a big bee in a small, but very active, hive.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Volunteer</title>
      <link>https://www.bsides.nz/volunteer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.bsides.nz/volunteer/</guid>
      <description>Volunteer Interested in helping at BSidesWLG 2017?
As a community-driven event, BSidesWLG would not be possible without the work of volunteers. The organisers are working hard to build a fun and exciting agenda. In order to execute this event and make it successful, we seeking volunteers to help with tasks before and on the two days of the event (November 23rd-24th, 2017), which include, but are not limited to:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to BSides Wellington</title>
      <link>https://www.bsides.nz/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.bsides.nz/</guid>
      <description>BSidesWLG is a diverse and inclusive information security conference welcoming anyone and everyone interested in security and security related topics. BSides is an open platform that provides a rare opportunity to share experiences, ideas, insights, and develop longstanding relationships with others in the security community.
Our 2017 conference will provide approximately 450 participants with the choice of 2 tracks that will cover a wide range of information security disciplines and topics!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>